[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which scientist discovered that blood could be separated into blood plasma and red blood cells and the components frozen separately, thus lasting longer?", "correct_answer": "Charles Drew", "incorrect_answers": ["Karl Landsteiner", "Paul Ehrlich", "Richard Keating"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the movie The Princes Diaries, what country does Queen Clarisse rule?", "correct_answer": "Genovia", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Sudan", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the blockbuster movie Forrest Gump?", "correct_answer": "Robert Zemeckis", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Soderbergh", "Tony Scott", "John Hughes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The daughter of what famous Italian singer and actor plays Satan in The Passion of the Christ?", "correct_answer": "Adriano Celentano", "incorrect_answers": ["Raffaele Riefoli", "Franco Battiato", "Albano Carrisi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal character does Ray Romano voice in the Ice Age 3 movie?", "correct_answer": "Mammoth", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiger", "Squirrel", "Dinosaur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do avocados contain?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Copper and manganese", "Vitamins B, vitamin K, vitamin E and vitamin C", "Omega 3 and omega 6 fatty acids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whisky is traditional for this country. The beverages color can give you a hint about its age.", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Wales", "USA", "Ireland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated film director worked on the 1990 crime movie Goodfellas?", "correct_answer": "Martin Scorsese", "incorrect_answers": ["Francis Ford Coppola", "Quentin Tarantino", "Oliver Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What relative of Norman Bates exists in his head as his alternate personality in the 1960 movie Psycho?", "correct_answer": "His mother", "incorrect_answers": ["His wife", "His father", "His sister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these oceans has the greatest depth?", "correct_answer": "Pacific Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean", "Arctic Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Following the success of the movie Clueless, there was a series of books based on the movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This hand game, also known as Roshambo, is used to randomly select a person for some purpose.", "correct_answer": "Rock, Paper, Scissors", "incorrect_answers": ["Thumb wrestling", "Odd or Even", "Hand jive"]}]